There, you see?  This is sent
to the customer's style office and this
is our number, our
organic cotton patent, so Global Organic
Textile Standard.  And this is a
certificate where we attest that the
cotton comes from
organic farming and the number is fundamental.
This is FSC, it comes from
industrial forests where trees are cut down but then
cyclically replanted.  This, for example, is
another RS ​​Responsible
Wool Standard certification.  Using sheep to
obtain wool is a job that man has
often done with scissors,
even cutting pieces of meat.
These certificates for animals like
RWS
certify that there are inspectors
who are making sure that the animals do not
suffer, but above all that there are no
children at work, that there is a
salary, an honest wage.  This is
another certificate.  This is the
standard responsible moire.  The Moer is
a goat, I
also see the Alpa here.
These are organic linen cottons.
This is the certificate for
polyesters of plastics that are
recycled.